smartsound.com 2019-06-08

# Privacy Policy

_This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.smartsound.com._

SmartSound LLC. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. SmartSound LLC. collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

In order for us to ship a demonstration CD of our software products, a user is required to give contact information (such as name, address and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. Incomplete or false information provided will result in us rejecting the request.

In the case of international demo requests, your information may be forwarded to a reseller in your area to assist you with demo questions and order fulfillment, as well as available documentation in your native language. Each reseller has their own privacy policy. A list of resellers in your area can be obtained by visiting here

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

We use a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. This company does not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, SmartSound LLC., are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

If a user wishes to subscribe to our email list, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. We do not share this information with any other company, and have no plans to do so.

This website takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing’. 

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email.

We send periodic email updates to our customers to let them know about new software releases, specials, updates, and other information. Members are able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone.

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user’s personal data provided to us. This can be done by emailing our Customer Service department.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google Inc. “(“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored there.

Google will reduce your IP address within Member States of the European Union or in other countries party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area beforehand. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened there. IP anonymization is active on this website. On behalf of the operator of this website, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports on website activity and to provide the website operator with other services relating to website and Internet use.

The IP address transmitted by your browser in the context of Google Analytics is not merged with other Google data. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. You can deactivate Google Analytics by click the Link at the bottom of this page. This will place an opt-out cookie only for this browser and for this domain. If you delete your browser cookies, you will have to opt-out again.

SMARTSOUND also uses 3rd party vendor re-marketing tracking cookies, including the Google Adwords tracking cookie. This means we will continue to show ads to you across the internet, specifically on the Google Content Network (GCN). As always we respect your privacy and are not collecting any identifiable information through the use of Google’s or any other 3rd party remarketing system.

The third-party vendors, including Google, whose services we use – will place cookies on web browsers in order to serve ads based on past visits to our website. – Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. This allows us to make special offers and continue to market our services to those who have shown interest in our service.

On our website, we use Google reCAPTCHA to monitor and prevent interactions on our website through automated access, in particular by bots. This is a service provided by Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043 USA, hereinafter referred to as "Google".

Through the certification according to EU-US Privacy Shield ,Google guarantees that the data protection requirements of the EU will also be complied with when processing data in the USA. ([https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt000000001L5AAI&status=Active))

This service enables Google to determine which website is sending a request and from which IP address you are using the so-called reCAPTCHA input box. The service includes the sending of the IP address and possibly other data that is necessary to provide and guarantee this service.

Please refer to <https://policies.google.com/privacy> for further information on the general handling of your user data.

To make the websites work properly many use cookies, which are small information files that are sent to your computer, mobile or other device when you visit the website and which will recognize your device on future visits. These types of files do a number of different jobs such as remembering your preferences and chosen items, assisting you to improve your site experience as well as trying to ensure that the adverts or offers you see online are more relevant to you.

This Website in particular may use cookies and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookies and tracking technology are useful for gathering information about your use of the Websites, information about your computer such as the computers IP address and browser type, demographic data, and information such as if you arrived at the Website via a link from a third-party site, in which case the cookie can provide information concerning the URL and information about the linking website.

Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology. However, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. If you are a registered user, this may include your name and e-mail address for verification purposes.

You may choose to set your web browser to not accept cookies. However, if you do not accept cookies, you will not be able to use all the services provided, sign in on any pages, post comments or make purchases, and you do not help us learn how to improve our Website, products, offers and marketing strategy.

The cookies used on this Website are the following:

Session cookies which are erased when you close the browser  
First-party cookies which are set by the web server of the visited page and share the same domain, and  
Third-party cookies stored by a different domain to the visited page’s domain. This can happen when the webpage references a file, such as JavaScript, located outside its domain.  
Session cookies are used to track and store items in the shopping cart to ensure a user is recognized when moving from page to page within the site and that any information entered is remembered. They are used only for this purpose and only accessible by this website.

Third-party cookies Web analytics software uses cookies to tell if a user has visited the site before, determine how many unique users we have and how often they visit the site.

These cookies cannot be used to identify individuals, they are used for aggregated statistics only. This allows us, for example, to tell which areas of the site are the most popular and better optimise our content for the interests of our users.

To allow users to share content with friends through social networks such as Facebook and Twitter we embed components provided by these third parties or build our own components which use their APIs. These third party companies have their own privacy policies and also policies for publishers which we will comply with.

Deactivate Google Analytics
